# CELESTE MICHEL

#### **About**

Age 23

Occupation Student Location Copenhagen

I'm a junior multimediadesigner. I currently study at Københavns Erhversakademi on 3rd semester. Before I started my study as a graphic designer, I was studying at home in my sparetime and taught myself some of the Adobe programs and learned about what graphic design is.

In 2019 I finished my art school course where I studied photography, architecture, design and ceramics.

Except my art school course I've worked for DFDS since 2018 until 2022.

I'm a very creative soul who always is crafting something. I love to paint, draw, do mini prototypes of architecture buildings, read books, or do my wall-decoration art. Oh and of course kryds&tværs! I love to explore and constantly learn new things, that 's what drives me everyday - learning!

### **Education**

- Multimediedesign KEA (2022-present)
- Art School Holbæk Kunsthøjskole (2019)
  - Studied Photography, design, architecture & ceramics
- HF Frederiksberg HF(2016-2018)
- Boarding School Skovbo Efterskole (2015-2016)



## **Proffessional skills**

Committed
Organized
Creative
Openminded
Flexible
Love learning
Team player
Selfdisciplined
Never late

# **Personality**

Motivated
Positive
Outgoing
Empath
Enjoy a good laugh
Creative

# Languages

Danish English Faroese Norwegian Beginner spanish

## **Experience**

- 2022 Medvirket for Lenovo
- 2021 Copenhagen Business School supervisor
- 2021 DFDS Crown Seaways, stewardess,
- 2021 Linda Andrews assistent
- 2021 Mads Heindorf Jewelry
- 2020 "A Christmas Miracle", Show
- 2020 Cafe Kystgården
- 2020 Modelling, ByGrønnbæk
- 2020 Hellerup Park Hotel
- 2019 Kunsthøjskolen i Holbæk

Studied photography, architecture, design and ceramics.

- 2019-Present Own company,
- 2018-Present Assistant for !LA Entertainment"
- 2018-2020 DFDS, Crown Seaways, stewardess,
- 2018-2020 DFDS, Crown Seaways, Barista, Espresso House
- 2018-2020 DFDS, Crown Seaways, Children's Entertainer
- 2017-2018 Danish Heart Foundation
- 2017-2019 CPH Airport, SAS Lounge
- 2017-2018 ByBiehl smykker
- 2017-2018 BeckSöndergaard
- 2017 Guilty Cupcakes

## Certificates

- First aid course passed
- Hygiene certificate
- CPH Medical School supervisor
- Barista certificate
- Maritime safety course
- Course included practical and theoretical trainings.
- PPL, Pilots Private Licence Standby
- "Social media" course
- Communication course
- Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator course
- Boat certificate
- Silva Method

# Important for me at a workplace

- Good communication and collaboration
- Teamwork
- Establish team rules
- Good vibe between collegues
- Openminded
- Respect and trust
- Being organized

#### **Tools**

#### Design

Figma Miro

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop

Adobe XD

Adobe InDesign

Wordpress

Pen & paper

#### Code

Visual Study Code Github HTML CSS

Javascript

## **CONTACT**

Tlf. nr.: +45 31763450 E-mail: celestemhp@gmail.com